Routing Number: 272477694

[

](https://www.facebook.com/zealcreditunion/)

[

](https://www.linkedin.com/company/zeal-credit-union/)

[

](https://twitter.com/zealcreditunion)

[

](https://www.instagram.com/zealcreditunion/)

[

](https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL3Ut66_hCUc3NHKA9NK74m7Q5g9xJFS-0)

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/locations/)

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/contact-us/)

[

](# "<? _e('Login and Personalize', 'zeal') ?>")

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/locations/)

Welcome!

Sign in to Online Banking:

Log In

* Personal
    * Products & Services
        * Checking
        * Savings
        * Loans
        * Credit Cards
        * Investments
    * Resources / Tools
        * Fraud Security & Prevention
        * Online Services
        * Tools
    * Member Benefits
    * About Us
* Business
    * Products & Services
        * Checking & Savings
            * Business Checking Accounts
        * Loans
    * Resources / Tools
        * Online Services
        * Tools
    * Member Benefits
        * Fraud Prevention
    * About Us

* Rates
    
    * [

        Mortgage
        
        For current rates, visit MortgageCenter.com/Zeal/rates/purchase](https://mortgagecenter.com/zeal/rates/purchase "Rates")
        
    * [

        Auto
        
        5.99%
        
        Rates as low as 5.99% APR\*](https://www.zealcu.org/rates/#auto_rates_anchor "Sample Page")
        
    * [

        CDs & IRAs
        
        1.00\-2.40%
        
        APY\*](https://www.zealcu.org/rates/#cds_ira_rates_anchor "Rates")
        
    * [

        Ultra Savings
        
        0.50\-0.80%
        
        APY\*](https://www.zealcu.org/rates/#savings_rates_anchor "Rates")

* Open an Account
    
    * WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO APPLY FOR?
        
    * [

        Become A Member](https://www.zealcu.org/become-a-member/ "Become A Member")
        
    * [

        Savings](https://www.zealcu.org/compare-savings-accounts/ "Savings")
        
    * [

        Loans](https://www.zealcu.org/loans/ "Loans")
        
    * [

        Credit Card](https://www.zealcu.org/visa-comparison/ "Credit Card")
        
    * [

        Mortgages](https://www.zealcu.org/home-loans/ "Mortgages")

    * Products & Services
    * Resources / Tools
    * Member Benefits
    * About Us
    * Products & Services
    * Resources / Tools
    * Member Benefits
    * About Us

    * [

        Mortgage
        
        For current rates, visit MortgageCenter.com/Zeal/rates/purchase](https://mortgagecenter.com/zeal/rates/purchase "Rates")
        
    * [

        Auto
        
        5.99%
        
        Rates as low as 5.99% APR\*](https://www.zealcu.org/rates/#auto_rates_anchor "Sample Page")
        
    * [

        CDs & IRAs
        
        1.00\-2.40%
        
        APY\*](https://www.zealcu.org/rates/#cds_ira_rates_anchor "Rates")
        
    * [

        Ultra Savings
        
        0.50\-0.80%
        
        APY\*](https://www.zealcu.org/rates/#savings_rates_anchor "Rates")

    * WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO APPLY FOR?
        
    * [

        Become A Member](https://www.zealcu.org/become-a-member/ "Become A Member")
        
    * [

        Savings](https://www.zealcu.org/compare-savings-accounts/ "Savings")
        
    * [

        Loans](https://www.zealcu.org/loans/ "Loans")
        
    * [

        Credit Card](https://www.zealcu.org/visa-comparison/ "Credit Card")
        
    * [

        Mortgages](https://www.zealcu.org/home-loans/ "Mortgages")

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/news-events/)

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/zeal-the-love/)

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/locations/)

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/contact-us/)

[

](# "<? _e('Login and Personalize', 'zeal') ?>")

[

](https://www.zealcu.org/)

Welcome!

Sign in to Online Banking:

Log In

What does Zeal Credit Union do with your personal information?
==============================================================

What does Zeal Credit Union do with your personal information?
==============================================================

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| FACTS | **WHAT DOES ZEAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?** |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| What? | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:  <br>• Social Security number and account balances  <br>• credit history and credit scores  <br>• income and payment history |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| How? | All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Zeal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. |

| **REASONS WE CAN SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION** | **DOES ZEAL CREDIT UNION SHARE?** | **CAN YOU LIMIT THIS SHARING?** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **For our everyday business purposes –**  <br>such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  |
| **For our marketing purposes –**  <br>to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  |
| **For joint marketing with other financial companies** **–** | Yes | No  |
| **For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –**  <br>information about your transactions and experiences | No  | We don’t share |
| **For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –**  <br>information about your creditworthiness | No  | We don’t share |

| **WHAT WE DO** |     |
| --- | --- |
| **How does Zeal Credit Union protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. |
| **How does Zeal Credit Union collect my personal information?** | We collect your personal information, for example, when you  <br>• open an account or deposit money  <br>• pay your bills or use your credit or debit card  <br>• or to apply for financing  <br>We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. |
| **Why can’t I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only  <br>• sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your credit worthiness  <br>• affiliates from using your information to market to you  <br>• sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you  <br>State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. |

| **DEFINITIONS** |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  <br>• Zeal Credit Union has no affiliates. |
| **Nonaffiliates** | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial  <br>and nonfinancial companies.  <br>• Zeal Credit Union does not share with our nonaffiliates so they can market  <br>to you. |
| **Joint Marketing** | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.  <br>• Our joint marketing partners include financial advisors and insurance companies. |

Zeal Credit Union Digital Privacy Policy
----------------------------------------

Zeal Credit Union has prepared a digital privacy policy to be used in conjunction with our standard Privacy Policy. Our standard Privacy Policy applies to both our digital and non-digital services. Our digital privacy policy is outlined below.

**Cookies and Information We Collect for Online Banking**

Cookies are a small text file assigned and attached by a web server to the directory file on your computer. If you conduct transactions with Zeal Credit Union via Online Banking, you may have noticed the use of temporary session cookies. These temporary session cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser and your information as you navigate and conduct transactions while you are logged into our Online Banking system. They help to keep your session active until you either log out of Online Banking or when the session automatically times out due to inactivity. Once any one of these conditions occurs, the temporary cookies are removed from your system and you must log in with your username and password to regain access to Online Banking.

**Cookies and Information We Collect at our Homepage**

We collect information from all visitors to our website regarding user behavior through the use of cookies. The use of cookies is designed to improve the end user experience, and all users remain anonymous while visiting our homepage. The information we collect includes which pages are accessed, duration of the visit, frequency of visits, geographic location, the devices and operating systems in use and other similar demographic data. Information obtained from our website is kept secure, and access to that information is limited to the credit union personnel and vendor partners who use that information to improve the Zeal Credit Union website.

**Online Banking Security Measurers**

Zeal Credit Union’s online banking website is a secured website. Our online banking website encrypts any data sent and received with Transport Layer Security (TLS) technology, which is used to provide a secure channel for data transmission across computer networks using public key cryptography. A website secured with the TLS protocol will cause a padlock to display in the URL address bar of a Microsoft browser, ensuring that data transmitted from that page cannot be altered when routed over the Internet. Browsers that do not support TLS are unable to access the Online Banking application. In addition, Zeal Credit Union employs the use of firewalls which are designed to protect our computer network from outside internet activity. These firewalls are regularly monitored to assure their security.

**Homepage Security Measures**

The Zeal Credit Union homepage website is a secured website. At the Zeal Credit Union homepage members may fill out applications for our products. We use Secured Socket Layer (SSL) technology on our website to encrypt any data that is sent or received. A website secured with the SSL protocol will cause a padlock to display in the URL address bar of a Microsoft browser, ensuring that data transmitted from that page cannot be altered when routed over the Internet. In addition, Zeal Credit Union employs the use of firewalls which are designed to protect our computer network from outside internet activity. These firewalls are regularly monitored to assure their security.

**Zeal Credit Union Mobile App**

iOS and Android platforms require that Zeal Credit Union provide our members with the ability to request the removal of their app accounts and any associated data. This requirement is the latest of many recent compliance updates from Google and Apple related to user privacy and data safety. If you would like to request the removal of your app accounts and related data, simply send an email request to: **[mxadmin@zealcu.org](mailto:mxadmin@zealcu.org)**. Please type “Remove App Account” in the subject line of your email and provide us with a good phone number at which to reach you. One of our representatives will be in touch with you to confirm the request is valid and initiate the process.

Upon execution of this request, Zeal Credit Union will delete all associated data held in our digital and internet banking system. This data will no longer be accessible or available to any party. Your accounts will remain active, and your account transaction history will remain in our main system history as long as your accounts are open, but all internet and Mobile Banking data will be deleted.

Some features included in digital banking may request access to data located on the device used to access digital banking. This may include biometric, camera, contacts, and location data. Users will be prompted to allow access to this data, and if access is not allowed, the feature requiring that data will not be fully functional.

**Links to 3rd Party Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites. Zeal Credit Union is not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. We encourage all users to read the privacy statement of all linked websites. When leaving our site for a site hosted by another company, you will receive a popup notice telling you that you are leaving our site, and users must accept or reject the prompt.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)**

Zeal Credit Union does not market to or collect data online for Rock Star Saver youth accounts, which includes all members age 0-11. For children ages 12-17 in the Nextgen program, we market to and collect data for our Online Banking product only. No other products and services requiring data collection online are knowingly marketed to children under the age of 13.

**Questions** If you have questions about our digital privacy policy, please contact:

Zeal Credit Union

17250 Newburgh Rd.

Livonia, MI 48152

Phone: [(800) 321-8570 Ext. 7400](tel:8003218570.7400)

E-mail: [memberservices@zealcu.org](mailto:memberservices@zealcu.org)

##### Leaving This Site

You are now leaving the Zeal Credit Union web site. Zeal Credit Union is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those websites that it does not operate and our Internet Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites. To remain at our site, click CLOSE. To leave our site for the link you selected, click ACCEPT. Thank you for visiting our site.

[Close](#) Accept

**Zeal Credit Union | 17250 Newburgh Road, Livonia, MI 48152 | 800-321-8570**

**Routing # 272477694**

download our mobile app

[

](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ifs.banking.fiid1532&hl=en_US)[

](https://apps.apple.com/us/app/zeal-credit-union-mobile/id900092853)

We do business in accordance with the Fair Housing Law and Equal Opportunity Credit Act.

**Your savings is federally insured to at least $250,000 and backed by the full faith and credit of the United States Government.**

We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website and for analytics. If you continue to use this site or click accept, you agree to our use of cookies and similar technologies.[Accept](#)[Privacy policy](https://www.zealcu.org/privacy-policy/)[](javascript:void(0);)

Help us personalize our site for you!

* First Name 
* Location
    
    Choose your branchAllen ParkAllen Park Drive-ThruDearbornDetroitLivonia - Middlebelt Rd.Livonia - Newburgh Rd.Lyon Crossing | Coming Soon!SouthfieldSouthgateTaylorWalled LakeWestland (🧡Drive-Thru Only on Saturdays)Woodhaven
    
* What are you here for?

    Savings

    Checking

    Loans

    Membership
    
* Personalize

Make your banking experience more personalized!

Tell us more about you.

No Thanks
